Friends, IC Lord is one of the best and most excellent companies.
We recruit here for the health insurance segment.
If we talk about health insurance, it is one of the best
companies whose claim settlement is very
superior. It has
tie-ups with more than 10,000 network hospitals. The
company settles claims in a very good and excellent manner.
Customers who take ICC Lombard policies here are
able to claim in hassle-free and tension-free policies. Any
health insurance is best
when the claim settlement is very
superior and very good. You will get to see and understand this special thing
in ICC Lombard.
As
[Sangeet]
[Prasha]
Hello friends, today we are going to talk about
how to become an agent in IC Lord.
IC Lord is one of the best and most
excellent companies, by joining which you will get tremendous
benefits. I will
tell you the entire process and will
give you information about the company and
how big will you earn after joining it.  You
can earn here,
I am going to share with you all the details of its working here.
My name is Yogendra Verma, Treatment
Manager, IC Lombard and my job is to
groom, train and
upgrade the system of people. You too can easily join a new and wonderful
working and
earn lakhs and crores of rupees easily.
Friends, before proceeding further in understanding this working carefully, it
is very important to subscribe to the channel, share, comment and click the bell icon, only then
you will keep getting all the latest updates. So let's
quickly understand what is ICC Lombard General
Insurance Company, since when has it been
working, for how long have you been working? Friends,
ICC Lord Company comes under one of the best and great companies.
Here
we do recruitment for the health insurance segment
and
if we talk about health insurance, then it is one of the best
company whose claim settlement is very
superior. It has
tie-ups with more than 10000 network hospitals. The
company settles claims in a very good and excellent manner.
Here, all the
customers who take ICC Lord policy,
They are able to claim in hassle-free, tension-free policies.
Any health
insurance is best when the
claim settlement is very superior.
You will see and understand this special thing at ICC Lombard.
As I tell you, the
health insurance segment is a booming sector.
Here, huge and excellent earnings
and working can be maintained. You can
work here on a part-time basis or on a
full-time basis. You can be a
professional, you can be employed, you can be
in business, you can be
in any professional activity, and if you also
want to work in the health insurance segment, then this is an amazing sector in itself, in
which your earnings can be
very big and very excellent.
Friends, this is a general insurance company. Here
you can work in three types of segments.
First, health insurance, then
motor insurance, and after motor, non-motor
insurance. All three types of platforms
are available here. However, we
apologize to those who want to get the ICC Lombard code only for motor insurance.
We do not provide them the code.
We provide
codes only for the health insurance segment
because I
am from the health vertical and my main focus is on health, due to
which we will
support you. You will get three managers, one
for health, one for motor and one
for non-motor, but you will get them only when
you work in health. To get the code here,
after getting the code, it will be
necessary to login in the first month for a policy with a
premium of Rs 15,000. To keep your policy
running for life long, for the first 5 years
you will have to take at least 12 health policies every year
so that your code continues, there is
no issue of any kind, there is no problem of any kind. Let's
talk about why this ICC
Lombard, because it has many
regions, in which the biggest region is that the
payout here is the best and good in the entire market.
You are going to get earnings from Rs 15 to Rs 40, which
you will not get in any other company,
this is the first big benefit here and the second one here  There are
monthly contests, quarterly
contests, and yearly clubs.
Along with this, domestic and international
trips are available, which are
fully paid by the company. And let me tell you one thing,
whenever you go on a trip with ICC Lord, it is an
unmatched trip. It is
so spectacular, so amazing, so wonderful, the
luxury of which you
will enjoy and will not forget in your lifetime. This is the power of
ICC Lombard's trips, and that entire
trip is fully paid.
You do not have to spend any money, whether you
go for a domestic trip or an
international trip, you will never
miss an ICC Lombard trip
whenever you join ICC Lord.
Secondly, you get paid
working here. What is the third important thing?
This is a completely digital platform. There is
no need to go to the branch for anything. The
company creates a learning environment here in a very excellent way.
All training is done
through Zoom meetings and Microsoft Teams, in
which working is very
easy.  We teach each and every thing in a digital way.
More than 500 agents are already working with us all over India.
You can also brighten your future with ICS Lombard. You can
learn new things in new ways in new working. You can
make a career in this along with your job, business or your professional working. Joining it is very
easy, for which a list of
documents has been given here. This list of documents will be given to
me through
WhatsApp. There will be one virtual interaction, only
after that we will process your code and then
you will have to pay an exam fee of ₹1.
Passing the exam is mandatory, only then you will
get this code, even if you are
coming to the health insurance segment for the first time. Even then, it
is necessary to appear in the exam. You have a
code of any life insurance company
or a code of any health insurance company,
despite that, if you want to
take the code of ICC Lombard or a code of a general insurance company, then appearing in the
exam will be mandatory, only then
you will get real access. There will be an exam fee of ₹1 and the
process will start only after paying it. The
exam takes 10 to 15 days.  After passing the exam in getting lined up,
you can join this working and
start it and friends, this
is a very good opportunity, you can easily earn from minimum
₹2500000 to 5 lakh, 10 lakh, 50 lakh per year
here,
you should not miss this opportunity.